# caitlin ironside

AN EYE FOR IDEAS

## **CAITLIN IRONSIDE** is a graphic

designer based in New York City.

With a unique sensitivity to detail and a relentless curiosity that could kill a cat, she prides herself on noticing that which is often overlooked. Favoring a conceptual, research-led approach to design, Caitlin is passionate about both the analytical and the abstract. She strives to create outcomes which possess intelligence, beauty, relevance, and simplicity. Her favorite projects are those in which love of typography and affinity for rich imagery can happily hold hands. To life's proverbial table she brings hard work, big dreaming, cheeky laughs, and a generous serving of sunshine.

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

## Niskayuna High School '13

Advanced Regents Diploma

## Binghamton University '18

- •Bachelor of Fine Arts Graphic Design
- •Bachelor of Arts Psychology

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

## Freelance Design / May 2015 - Present

•Managed various branding, print, and web projects.

# The Invisible Illnesses / July 2017-Present Creative Director

- •Designed social media content for multiple platforms.
- •Maintained organization's website.
- •Designed monthly newsletter.
- •Designed apparel.

## Pipe Dream / August 2017-December 2017

- •Designed layouts for all sections and resolved layout issues.
- •Constructed advertisements and infographics.
- •Communicated with Photo Department.

### SKILLS

- •Front-end Coding (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- •Layout & Typography
- Illustration & Animation
- Product Photography
- Photo Editing
- •Branding & Packaging
- •E-mail Marketing